Giulio V. Blanc
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Biographical Files, 1994-1995, undated, Series 1:; (box 1; 3 folders)
  Included is a page of Blanc's resume, a self-written biography, and a letter from The Graduate School and University Center (CUNY) advancing Blanc to candidacy for a doctoral degree in art history. Also found is a press release for a 1995 panel discussion and a New York University Museum Studies newsletter which mentions Blanc's exhibition, Wifredo Lam and His Contemporaries at the Studio Museum in Harlem, and other miscellaneous material.
  - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Letter, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Miscellany, 1995 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
- Miscellaneous Letters, 1983-1995, undated, Series 2:; (box 1; 3 folders)
  Letters in Spanish and English to Blanc from artists and friends and to Blanc's parents Lodovico and Maria V. Blanc; arranged chronologically.
  - Letters, 1983-1995, undated, (3 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5476)
- Artist Files, 1920-1995, undated, Series 3:; (boxes 1-8; 6 linear ft.)
  This extensive series contains artist files Giulio Blanc collected and arranged alphabetically by name of artist. The files contain scattered correspondence, newspaper clippings, original writings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and miscellaneous materials.
  Several of the artist files are further broken down into areas such as Biographical Material, Letters, Writings, Notes, Printed Material, Audio material, and Photographs. Examples of Biographical material include curricula vita and resumes, fellowship applications, copies of birth certificates, written statements by artists concerning their work, and brief reference information written by Blanc about the artists and their artwork.
  Letters are from art institutions, artists, curators, art historians and friends and are addressed primarily to Giulio Blanc, although a number of letters are addressed to other individuals. Found are original letters, photocopies, or facsimiles and occasionally include attachments such as exhibition announcements, newspaper clippings or photographs. Greeting cards and postcards are also found here.
  Writings consists of unpublished material such as draft copies of essays and articles, papers written for courses, as well as poems, journal entries, and other original writings. Printed material includes exhibition announcements and catalogs, public program brochures, invitations to exhibition openings, and published articles and newspaper clippings. These are recorded by name of item.
  In addition, the artists files also house interviews conducted by Blanc and recorded on audio cassette tape. Those interviewed are artist Enrique Riverón, curator José Gomez Sícre, Cuban ethnographer Lydia Cabrera speaking on the work of Wifredo Lam (Wifredo Lam files), Eva Frajaville on Agustin Fernández (Agustin Fernández files), and Elena Peláez de Medero discussing the work of her sister, Amelia Peláez (Amelia Peláez files).
  Of special interest in this series are a number of documents in the files of artists Wifredo Lam, Amelia Peláez and Enrique Riverón. These include rare exhibition announcements and invitations, exhibition catalogs, clippings from European newspapers and various other original documents that date from the 1920s-1990s. An itemized list of these documents is found in the Appendix
  - Disk and printed document from disk, “Files of Cuban Artists”, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Eduardo Abela (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Articles, 1930, 1949 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, 1950-1960, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Juan Abreu Felippe (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1982, 1985 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements and pamphlet, 1984, 1993, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1984, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1981, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Gustavo Acosta (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, newspaper clippings and articles, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Orlando Acosta (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1995 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - A. Acosta-Leon (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, articles, and photographs, 1956, 1983, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Juan Adriaensens (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, exhibition catalogs, 1980, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Rene Aguilar (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photo transparencies, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Carmen Aldunate (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Ramon Alejandro (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1970-1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement, catalogs, and invitations, 1981, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989-1992, undated resume, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs and post cards, 1969, 1983-1988, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Carlos Alfonzo (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1982-1997, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Writings, draft articles on Carlos Alfonzo by Giulio Blanc, 1993, 1996 and, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Notes, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1983-1993, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1982-1993, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1976-1990 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photocopies of drawings w/ writing, 1982 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Mario Algaze (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1983 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, 1979, 1981 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Luis Alonso (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, n.d (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Marcos Alvarez (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1993 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Carlos Alves (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement and newspaper clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Alejandro Anreus (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements and small catalogs, 1980-1981, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalog, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Jorge Arche (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photograph, 1945 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Enrique Arredondo (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1970 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - John Asencion (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement and poster, 1979 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1979 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Waldo Balart (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, pamphlets, and posters, 1966, 1969, 1977 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Luisa Basnuevo (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1992, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photo transparencies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Lilliam Becker (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1976 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - José Bedia (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Writings, draft articles on José Bedia by Giulio Blanc, 1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalog, 1992-1994, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1992-1995, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Press releases, 1995, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs and photo transparency, 1992, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Jaime Bellachasse (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Press release, 1982 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photo transparencies, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Elio Beltran (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1976, 1980, 1986 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalogs and articles, 1983-1984, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photo transparencies, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Mario Bencomo (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1982-1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Writings, draft article on Mario Bencomo by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1980-1992 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Press release, 1989 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1984-1993, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - César Bermudez (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1983 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Cundo Bermúdez (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letter, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Notes, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1942-1979, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1943-1997, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1940-1980s, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - José Bermudez (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1975, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1953-1981, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Jose Bernardo (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1989 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Carlos Bentacourt (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1995, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Guido Betancourt (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Writings, essay on Guido Betancourt by Florencio García Cisneros, 1977 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1976, 1978 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Agustin Blazquez (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Juan Boza (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcement and invitations, 1974, 1988, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1983, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Francisco Brennand (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Ernesto Briel (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1974, 1988, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Press releases, 1988 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Articles, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photo transparencies, 1988 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Rolando Briseño-Dirube (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1982 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Maria Brito (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Letters, 1980, 1990 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1980-1994, undated (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
    - Photographs, 1983 (Box 1, Reel 5476)
  - Lydia Cabrera (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letter, 1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Notes and descriptive information on Lydia Cabrera exhibition, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1984 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1977-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Servando Cabrera (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1978, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Humberto Calzada (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1979-1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles and Vanidades magazine, 1978-1991, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Jorge Camacho (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1960-1983, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition brochures and catalogs, 1982-1984, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Maria Magdalena Campos-Pons (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Pablo Cano (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letter, 1985 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Writings, Tía Carmela: A Cuban Tragicomedy by Giulio V. Blanc with illustrations by Pablo Cano [Unpublished], sketches and price lists, 1991-1993, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1981-1993, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs and negatives, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Maria Capdevila Casas (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Writings, essay on Capdevila Casas, no author, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clipping, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Galaor Carbonell (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Manuel Carbonell (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1995, nd (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Agustin Cárdenas (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog and newspaper clipping, 1979, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Carlos Cardenas (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Alberto Carol (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1992 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Mario Carreño (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Writings, draft articles on Mario Carreño by Giulio Blanc, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1941-1981 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalogs and invitation, 1991-1995, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1939-1995, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1939-1948, 1953, 1993 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Miscellany, photocopies of artworks and price lists, 1981-1993, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Ramon Carulla (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letter, 1993 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Writings, draft articles on Ramon Carulla by Giulio Blanc, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1980-1994, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1985 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings and Vanidades magazine, 1980-1987, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Consuelo Castañeda (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcement and catalog, press release, newspaper clipping, 1992, 1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Eloisa Castellanos (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Michael Castellon (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Claudio Castillo (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material and newspaper article, 1977, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photo transparency, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Humberto Castro (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Writings, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, catalogs, press release, newspaper clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Humberto Catá (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1990 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Mirta Cerra (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1953, 1955 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Humberto Chavez (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and posters, 1983-1985, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Aleandro Colunga (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalog, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Hugo Consuegra (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1969, 1981 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Rafael Consuegra (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Enrique J. Crucet (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog and poster, 1993, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Emilio Antonio Cruz (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Luis Cruz Azaceta (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1978, 1985-1986 and undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Notes, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1978, 1992-1994, n,d (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1982-1985, 1993, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Press releases, 1985-1986, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper articles and clippings, magazine, Arte en Colombia, 1985-1986, 1994, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Miscellany, price lists, magazine covers and posters, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Miguel Cubiles (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1981 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Arturo Cuenca (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1992, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Notes, 1993 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1992 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1990 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989-1992, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs and photo transparency, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Hermanos Curras (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Pedro Damian (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letter, 1982 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Ana Albertina Delgado (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Demi (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, 1991, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1988, 1993, 1997, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1991-1997, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Miscellany, price lists, 1991, n.d (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Roberto Diago (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, 1947, 1992, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Nelson Diaz (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcement and press release, 1994 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Carmen Diaz-Oñate (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1982 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Humberto Dionisio (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Letters, 1990 (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1982, 1987, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1976-1977, 1981, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Miscellany, list of artworks for exhibition, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Vicente Dopico (Box 2, Reel 5477)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 2, Reel 5477)
  - Antonia Eiriz (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, draft essay and transcribed interview [Incomplete], 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Notes, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1993 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1994, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Eladio (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Ramon Elozua (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Carlos Enriquez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters, 1949, 1951, 1995 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, essays by Alejandro Anreus [Incomplete] and Alfredo Lozano, 1986, 1990, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1943, 1945, 1957, 1979, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1941, 1985, 1988-1989, 1995, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs, 1943, 1946, 1956, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Eberto Escobedo Lazo (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Tomas Esson (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, exhibition announcement and catalog, article, 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Roberto Estopiñan (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalog, press release, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clipping, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Price list and photo transparencies, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Alberto Falcon (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Emilio Falero (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, writings on Velazquez's Las Meniñas, exhibition announcements and catalog, newspaper clippings, 1970s-1990s (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Agustin Fernández (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters, 1977, 1988-1993, (3 folders) (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, draft articles on Agustin Fernández by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Notes, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1955-1978-1992 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Press release, 1980 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1951-1992, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Audio material, interview with Eva Frejaville on artist Agustin Fernandez, audio cassette tape, 1990 [Untranscribed, Spanish] (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs, 1950-1980, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Miscellany, napkin with handwriting by A. Fernandez, other material, 1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Aristides Fernandez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, published essay on Aristides Fernández by J. Lozama Lima, 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Jesse Fernandez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material and published article on Jesse Fernandez by Guillermo Cabrera Infante, 1980, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Joaquin Ferrer (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Humberto Figueras (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Moises Finalé (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letter and postcards, 1992 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1987-1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Rafael Fornes (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Laser color copies of artwork, 1993, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Luciano Franchi de Alfaro (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1985-1986, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Camilo Franqui (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition catalog and newspaper clipping, 1988, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Agustin Gainza (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, price list, photograph, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Alvaro Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, exhibition announcement (poster), newspaper article, photographs, photo transparencies, 1983-1984, 1994, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Fernando Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1980-1985, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photograph and photo transparencies, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Gay Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition brochures, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photo transparencies, 1984, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Hernan Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - J. Gil Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)